Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series B: Individual Portraits, September 1937-September 1938, 10865
  - Photo Unit #: B720 Corporal Leonard Holtzclaw, Lincoln-Washington, Company 3 cited, Aug 1938; 10896 (Item 11-0058)
  - Photo Unit #: B721 Corporal Jack Barrett, Lincoln-Washington, Company 3 cited, Aug 1938; 10895 (Item 11-0059)
  - Photo Unit #: B723 Sandor Voros, Chief of Commissariat, Aug 1938; 10894 (Item 11-0060)
  - Photo Unit #: B724 Abraham Smorodin, MacKenzie-Papineau, Aug 1938; 10893 (Item 11-0232)
  - Photo Unit #: B725 Abraham Smorodin, MacKenzie-Papineau, Aug 1938; 10892 (Item 11-0233)
  - Photo Unit #: B726 David Gordon, Commissariat, Aug 1938; 10891 (Item 11-0234)
  - Photo Unit #: B728 Sandor Voros, Commissariat, Aug 1938; 10890 (Item 11-0235)
  - Photo Unit #: B729 Ernest Amatniek, Transmiciones [Transmissions], Aug 1938; 10889 (Item 11-0236)
  - Photo Unit #: B730 Ben Barsky, MacKenzie-Papineau, Aug 1938; 10888 (Item 11-0237)
  - Photo Unit #: B731 John O'Hara, MacKenzie-Papineau, Aug 1938; 10887 (Item 11-0238)
  - Photo Unit #: B732 Harry Schoenberg, MacKenzie-Papineau, Aug 1938; 10886 (Item 11-0239)
  - Photo Unit #: B734 Antonio Pujol, Comisariado [Commissariat], Sep 1938; 10885 (Item 11-0240)
  - Photo Unit #: B736 David (Red) Drummond, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938; 10884 (Item 11-0061)
  - Photo Unit #: B737 Harry Hakam, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938; 10883 (Item 11-0062)
  - Photo Unit #: B738 Lieutenant David Smith, Company 4, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938; 10882 (Item 11-0241)
  - Photo Unit #: B739 Lieutenant David Smith, Company 4, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938; 10881 (Item 11-0242)
  - Photo Unit #: B740 Lieutenant William Wheeler, Company 4, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938; 10880 (Item 11-0243)
  - Photo Unit #: B741 Lawrence Lustgarten, undated; 10879 (Item 11-1315)
  - Photo Unit #: B742 Borzidor Dakic, special Machine-Gunner Company (Yugoslav), Sep 1938; 10878 (Item 11-0244)
  - Photo Unit #: B743 Benjamin (Butch) Goldstein, MacKenzie-Papineau, Sep 1938; 10877 (Item 11-0245)
  - Photo Unit #: B744 Ernst Lesser, Commissariat, Sep 1938; 10876 (Item 11-0246)
  - Photo Unit #: B745 Benito Rodriguez, chauffeur, Sep 1938; 10875 (Item 11-0247)
  - Photo Unit #: B746 Jacob Elias Cohen, oficina, Sep 1938; 10874 (Item 11-0248)
  - Photo Unit #: B750 Armando Torres Diaz, Commissariat, 59th Brigade, Sep 1938; 10873 (Item 11-0249)
  - Photo Unit #: B751 Constantino Dubas, Adjuntant Commissar, 59th Brigade, Sep 1938; 10872 (Item 11-0250)
  - Photo Unit #: B754 Archie Brown, Commissar, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938; 10871 (Item 11-0251)
  - Photo Unit #: B755 Melchor Rajon, Commissar, Company 1, 59th Battalion, Sep 1938; 10870 (Item 11-0252)
    Available Formats: Original Negative
  - Photo Unit #: B761 Lawrence Cohen [alias Larry Cane], Commissar, Company 1, 59th Battalion, Sep 1938; 10869 (Item 11-0253)
  - Photo Unit #: B762 Carlos Arias, Commissar, Company 1, 59th Battalion, Sep 1938; 10868 (Item 11-0254)
  - Photo Unit #: B764 Sergeant Louis Gayle, Sanidad [Health], Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938; 10867 (Item 11-0255)
  - Photo Unit #: B766 David Doran, Jan 1937; 10866 (Item 11-0691)
- Series C: Group Portraits, September 1937-August 1938., 10605
  Series IIC: Group Portraits, September 1937 - August 1938, consists of 259 images, which range from double portraits of volunteers casually posing to more formal group photos of entire units. Included here are the Lincoln Washington Machine-Gunner Company, officers of British Anti-Tank Unit, the 15th International Brigade Transmiciones (the unit in charge of communication or transmission); the 24th Spanish Battalion Machine-Gunner Company; the motor cyclists of 15th Brigade; the Lincoln-Washington ambulance and medical personnel; Earl Browder and officers of the 15th International Brigade; Greeks in the Lincoln Battalion; an African-American machine-gunner crew; Doctor Edward Barsky and a medical colleague; Captain Leonard Lamb with Lieutenant William Digges; and five New York University students -- volunteers with the Abraham Lincoln Brigade.
  - Photo Unit #: C001 Lincoln-Washington food truck at Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10864 (Item 11-0692)
  - Photo Unit #: C002 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner, group 2, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10863 (Item 11-0694)
  - Photo Unit #: C003 Lincoln-Washington Battalion eating, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10862 (Item 11-0693)
  - Photo Unit #: C004 Two Armenians, Lincoln-Washington, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10861 (Item 11-0695)
  - Photo Unit #: C005 [?] Neilson (l.) and Kenneth Brown, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10860 (Item 11-1316)
  - Photo Unit #: C006 G. Dilich (l.) and Kenneth Brown, Lincoln-Washington, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10859 (Item 11-0696)
  - Photo Unit #: C007 First aid men of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Sep 1937; 10858 (Item 11-0697)
  - Photo Unit #: C008 Lincoln-Washington kitchen, Senes, Oct 1937; 10857 (Item 11-0698)
  - Photo Unit #: C009 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company, rain, Senes, Oct 1937; 10856 (Item 11-0699)
  - Photo Unit #: C010 Lincoln-Washington kitchen, Senes, Oct 1937; 10855 (Item 11-0700)
  - Photo Unit #: C011 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company pay day, Senes, Oct 1937; 10854 (Item 11-0701)
  - Photo Unit #: C012 [?] Gordon (l.) and John Robinson, Asst. Political Commissar of 15th Brigade, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937; 10853 (Item 11-0702)
  - Photo Unit #: C013 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company and Sec. 1, Sep 1937; 10852 (Item 11-0703)
  - Photo Unit #: C014 Joe Bianca, Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company, Sec. 2, Crew 3, Sep 1937; 10851 (Item 11-0704)
  - Photo Unit #: C015 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company Sec. 2, Crew 4, Sep 1937; 10850 (Item 11-0705)
  - Photo Unit #: C016 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company Sec. 1, Crew 2, Sep 1937; 10849 (Item 11-0706)
  - Photo Unit #: C017 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company Sec. 3, Crew 5, Sep 1937; 10848 (Item 11-0707)
  - Photo Unit #: C018 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company Sec. 3, Crew 6 (Spanish), Sep 1937; 10847 (Item 11-0708)
  - Photo Unit #: C020 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gu officers: Milton Wolff, Mike Pappas, Zip Kachinski, 308153 (Item 11-1820)
  - Photo Unit #: C021 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Runners, Sep 1937; 10846 (Item 11-0709)
  - Photo Unit #: C022 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company post office, Almuchel: [?] Brown, Battalion Postman, [?] Wilson, Brigade Postman, Sep 1937; 10845 (Item 11-0710)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/23)
  - Photo Unit #: C023 John Robinson (l.) and Captain Leonard Lamb, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937; 10844 (Item 11-0711)
  - Photo Unit #: C024 John Robinson (l.), Philip Detro and Captain Leonard Lamb, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937; 10843 (Item 11-0712)
  - Photo Unit #: C025 Philip Detro (l.) and Captiain Leonard Lamb, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937; 10842 (Item 11-0713)
  - Photo Unit #: C026 Carl Geiser (l.), Philip Detro and Captain Leonard Lamb, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937; 10841 (Item 11-0714)
  - Photo Unit #: C027 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Staff, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10840 (Item 11-0715)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/4)
  - Photo Unit #: C028 Lincoln-Washington ambulance and medical personnel, Sep 1937; 10839 (Item 11-1817)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/17)
  - Photo Unit #: C029 Officers of Company 1, 24th Battalion, undated; 10717 (Item 11-1788)
    (Moscow Number: 5/183/37)
  - Photo Unit #: C030 Lieutenant Commander Abad Garcia of the 24th Battalion (left); José María Varela, Political Commissar of the 24th Battalion (right), Sep 1937; 10712 (Item 11-1787)
    (Moscow Number: 5/183/36)
  - Photo Unit #: C032 Officers and Political Delegates of Company 2, 24th Battalion, Sep 1937; 10704 (Item 11-1790)
    (Moscow Number: 5/183/42)
  - Photo Unit #: C033 Comrades of 24th Battalion who captured Fascist Commander Santapu and Lieutenant Colonel San Martin, Sep 1937; 10701 (Item 11-1789)
    (Moscow Number: 5/183/41)
  - Photo Unit #: C035 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Sep 1937; 369367 (Item 11-1885)
  - Photo Unit #: C037 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10838 (Item 11-0716)
  - Photo Unit #: C038 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10837 (Item 11-0717)
  - Photo Unit #: C039 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10836 (Item 11-0718)
  - Photo Unit #: C040 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10835 (Item 11-0719)
  - Photo Unit #: C041 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Sep 1937; 369368 (Item 11-1886)
  - Photo Unit #: C042 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10834 (Item 11-0720)
  - Photo Unit #: C043 Harry Poll speaking at meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10833 (Item 11-0721)
    (Moscow Number: 5/183/40)
  - Photo Unit #: C044 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10832 (Item 11-0722)
  - Photo Unit #: C045 David Doran addressing meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10831 (Item 11-0723)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/27)
  - Photo Unit #: C050 M. Constant [?] (l.) and G.R. Dias [?], Ambite, Nov 1937; 10830 (Item 11-0724)
  - Photo Unit #: C051 15th Brigade Armorers, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Sep 1937; 10829 (Item 11-0976)
  - Photo Unit #: C052 15th Brigade Armorers, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Sep 1937; 10828 (Item 11-0725)
  - Photo Unit #: C056 Joseph Dougher (l.) and Carl Bradley, Captain of 24th Battalion, American Company, Oct 1937; 10827 (Item 11-0726)
  - Photo Unit #: C058 Pat Reid (l.) and Harry Fisher, Oct 1937; 10826 (Item 11-0727)
  - Photo Unit #: C059 Joseph Dougher, Commissar, MacKenzie-Papineau, Company 3 (l.), Albert (Abe) Harris, Brigade Intendencia, and Wally Sabatini, Political Commissar, MacKenzie-Papineau, Company 3, Oct 1937; 10825 (Item 11-0728)
  - Photo Unit #: C060 New York University Volunteers: Leonard B. Levenson, Paul Sigel, Emanuel Mandel, Elkan Wendkos, ?; and Paul MacEachron (Oberlin College), at Azaila, Spain, Oct 1937; 10824 (Item 11-0729)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/3)
  - Photo Unit #: C061 Carl Bradley (l.) and Radomir Smrcka, 15th Brigade Information Service, Oct 1937; 10823 (Item 11-0730)
  - Photo Unit #: C063 Robert Thompson, Battalion Commander of 15th International Brigade, MacKenzie-Papineau (l.), Philip Detro of Lincoln-Washington, [?] Garcia 24th, [?] O'Dair (British) and [?] Aguila 24th Battalion, Oct 1937; 10822 (Item 11-0731)
  - Photo Unit #: C064 Rollin Dart (l.), Captain of Brigade staff, and David Doran, Oct 1937; 10821 (Item 11-1317)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/32)
  - Photo Unit #: C067 Officers of British anti-tank [unit:] Bill Alexander (left) P. D., Hugh Slater, [?], Oct 1937; 10820 (Item 11-1318)
  - Photo Unit #: C068 Anti-Tank Unit leaders, undated; 10819 (Item 11-1319)
  - Photo Unit #: C071 15th Brigade Transmissions at Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10818 (Item 11-0732)
  - Photo Unit #: C072 15th Brigade Transmissions at Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10817 (Item 11-0733)
  - Photo Unit #: C074 Officers of Lincoln-Washington Company 3, Com. Sancha [?], Murielo [?], and Florentino Alejo Ortiz [?], Political Commissar, Almuchel, Oct 1937; 10816 (Item 11-0734)
  - Photo Unit #: C075 Cubans in Lincoln-Washington, Company 3, Sep 1937; 10815 (Item 11-0735)
  - Photo Unit #: C076 Lincoln-Washington Section 3, Company 3, Sep 1937; 10814 (Item 11-0736)
  - Photo Unit #: C079 Greeks in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10813 (Item 11-0737)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/28)
  - Photo Unit #: C080 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 3, Sec. 3, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10812 (Item 11-0738)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/3)
  - Photo Unit #: C081 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 3, Sec. 4, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10811 (Item 11-0739)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/6)
  - Photo Unit #: C082 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 3 officers (5) Mouton, (6) William Miller, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10810 (Item 11-0740)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/29)
  - Photo Unit #: C083 Spanish in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 3, Section 3, Almuchel; [nine soldiers], Sep 1937; 10809 (Item 11-1819)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/26)
  - Photo Unit #: C084 Spanish comrades of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10808 (Item 11-1822)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/40)
  - Photo Unit #: C085 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 1, Group 1, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10807 (Item 11-0741)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/18)
  - Photo Unit #: C086 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 3, Group 1, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10806 (Item 11-0742)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/24)
  - Photo Unit #: C087 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 2, Group 1, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10805 (Item 11-0743)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/21)
  - Photo Unit #: C088 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 1, Group 2, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10804 (Item 11-0744)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/22)
  - Photo Unit #: C090 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 2, Group 3, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10803 (Item 11-0745)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/9)
  - Photo Unit #: C091 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Section 3, Group 2, Almuchel; [three soldiers with a machine gun], Sep 1937; 10802 (Item 11-1818)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/19)
  - Photo Unit #: C092 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 3, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10801 (Item 11-0746)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/41)
  - Photo Unit #: C093 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 3, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10800 (Item 11-0747)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/10)
  - Photo Unit #: C094 Officers, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sep 1937; 10799 (Item 11-0748)
  - Photo Unit #: C095 Officers and Company Staff, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Sep 1937; 10798 (Item 11-0749)
  - Photo Unit #: C096 Officers and Company Staff, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Sep 1937; 10797 (Item 11-0750)
  - Photo Unit #: C097 Kenneth Brown, Company 1 Political Commissar and Political Delegate, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10796 (Item 11-0977)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/7)
  - Photo Unit #: C098 Scouts of the Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Almuchel, [four soldiers], Sep 1937; 10795 (Item 11-1814)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/8)
  - Photo Unit #: C099 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 1, Group 3, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10794 (Item 11-0751)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/37)
  - Photo Unit #: C100 Comrades from Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sep 1937; 10793 (Item 11-0752)
  - Photo Unit #: C101 David Doran (c.), Political Commissar, 15th Brigade, John Robinson (r.), Asst. Political Commissar, 15th Brigade, Sep 1937; 10792 (Item 11-0753)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/31)
  - Photo Unit #: C103 Group at 15th International Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters] at Ambite, Nov 1937; 10791 (Item 11-0754)
  - Photo Unit #: C104 Group at waterbarrel: Ivan Rujevcic [alias John Gerlach], Robert Merriman, Rollin Dart, David Doran and John Robinson (second from l.-r.), Sep 1937; 10790 (Item 11-0755)
  - Photo Unit #: C105 Ivan Rujevcic [alias John Gerlach] (l.) and David Doran, Oct 1937; 10789 (Item 11-0756)
  - Photo Unit #: C107 David Doran (l.), Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic and Captain Radomir Smrcka, Ambite, Nov 1937; 10788 (Item 11-0978)
  - Photo Unit #: C108 Harry Pollitt, David Doran, Radomir Smercka, Vladimir Copic, Major Germina Galleani, "Max," Ambite, Nov 1937; 10787 (Item 11-1759)
    (Moscow Number: 5/177/29)
  - Photo Unit #: C109 David Doran, Elias Begelman, Vladimir Copic, "Max", Major Germina Galleani, Ambite, Nov 1937; 10786 (Item 11-1758)
    Available Formats: Moscow negative
    (Moscow Number: 5/177/17)
  - Photo Unit #: C110 Umberto Galliani, Garibaldi Brigade [12th], undated; 10785 (Item 11-1321)
  - Photo Unit #: C111 Elias Begelman, Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, [?], Galleani, Dunbar at Ambite, Nov 1937; 10784 (Item 11-1322)
  - Photo Unit #: C114 Robert Merriman, [?] and Vladimir Copic, Sep 1937; 10783 (Item 11-0757)
    (Moscow Number: 5/177/31)
  - Photo Unit #: C120 British Anti-tank and kitchen, Nov 1937; 10782 (Item 11-0063)
  - Photo Unit #: C126 Abraham Eisenberg and [?] Shapiro (deserter), Nov 1937; 10781 (Item 11-0979)
  - Photo Unit #: C128 James Bourne (l.) and David Doran, Nov 1937; 10780 (Item 11-0758)
  - Photo Unit #: C129 Frank Ryan (l.) and John Robinson, Oct 1937; 10779 (Item 11-0759)
  - Photo Unit #: C130 David Doran (l.) and John Robinson, Oct 1937; 10778 (Item 11-0760)
  - Photo Unit #: C131 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] staff at Senes, Oct 1937; 10777 (Item 11-0761)
  - Photo Unit #: C134 British Battalion, F. Doysle [?], Company 3 Political Commissar; F. Madigan [?], Company 3 Commander, Senes, Oct 1937; 10776 (Item 11-1794)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/5)
  - Photo Unit #: C135 British Battalion Serano Com. [?] Company 4, Senes, Oct 1937; 10775 (Item 11-0980)
  - Photo Unit #: C137 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, kitchen [serving food] [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Oct 1937; 369369 (Item 11-1887)
  - Photo Unit #: C139 Kitchen staff, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Oct 1937; 10774 (Item 11-0762)
  - Photo Unit #: C140 Ivan Rujevcic (l.) and Rollin Dart, Quinto, Oct 1937; 10773 (Item 11-0763)
  - Photo Unit #: C141 M[?] Safir (l.) and David Doran at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10772 (Item 11-0764)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/25)
  - Photo Unit #: C143 José María Mateo Sastre, Asst. Commissar of 15th Brigade, and David Doran, Oct 1937; 10771 (Item 11-0765)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/29)
  - Photo Unit #: C144 Albert Chisholm (l.) and George Waters, Oct 1937; 10770 (Item 11-1323)
  - Photo Unit #: C145 Doctor Mark Straus (l.) and Major Robert Merriman at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10769 (Item 11-0766)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/1)
  - Photo Unit #: C146 Spanish solidiers of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion at rest in Quinto after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10768 (Item 11-1832)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/16)
  - Photo Unit #: C147 Ukranians of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion at rest after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10767 (Item 11-1835)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/24)
  - Photo Unit #: C148 Machine-Gunner Company of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10766 (Item 11-0767)
  - Photo Unit #: C149 [?] (l.) and Eugene Nolte after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10765 (Item 11-0768)
  - Photo Unit #: C150 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10764 (Item 11-1836)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/25)
  - Photo Unit #: C151 Spaniards of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion at rest after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10763 (Item 11-1840)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/33)
  - Photo Unit #: C152 [?] (l.), [?] and Jack Thomas after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10762 (Item 11-0769)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/17)
  - Photo Unit #: C155 15th Brigade cyclists Abraham Irving Halpern, Robert Minor and John Burning, Oct 1937; 10761 (Item 11-0981)
  - Photo Unit #: C156 Brigade Scouts at Quinto after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10760 (Item 11-1782)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/15)
  - Photo Unit #: C158 Robert Minor (l.), [?] and [?] at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Quinto, Oct 1937; 10759 (Item 11-0770)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/13)
  - Photo Unit #: C160 British Battalion Medical Corps, Oct 1937; 10758 (Item 11-0256)
  - Photo Unit #: C161 Vladimir Copic and Robert Merriman, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10757 (Item 11-0258)
  - Photo Unit #: C162 Robert Merriman and Rollin Dart, Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10756 (Item 11-0257)
  - Photo Unit #: C168 Brigade Scouts, Ambite, Captain Radomir Smrcka in charge, Nov 1937; 10755 (Item 11-0982)
  - Photo Unit #: C169 Brigade Scouts, Ambite, Captain Radomir Smrcka in charge, Nov 1937; 10754 (Item 11-0983)
  - Photo Unit #: C172 Eugene Poling (l.) and "Doc" James Hill, both from Oklahoma and received citations, Nov 1937; 10753 (Item 11-0984)
  - Photo Unit #: C190 Colin Charles "Doc" Bradsworth and practicantes of the MacKenzie-Papineau, Nov 1937; 10752 (Item 11-0985)
  - Photo Unit #: C193 First-aid class at MacKenzie-Papineau, Nov 1937; 10751 (Item 11-0986)
  - Photo Unit #: C198 Group {Transmiciones?}; Louis Stoloff, at right, front row, undated; 308657 (Item 11-0986A)
  - Photo Unit #: C199 Brigade Topographers Albert Kohn (l.), Hans Gutman and Doug [Orville Douglas] Taylor, Nov 1937; 10750 (Item 11-0987)
  - Photo Unit #: C200 Herman "Gabby" Klein (l.) and Louis Eider at Ambite, Nov 1937; 10748 (Item 11-0988)
  - Photo Unit #: C201[?] Lincoln-Washington machine-gun officers: Milton Wolff, Mike Pappas, Zip Kachinski, and three others, undated; 10749 (Item 11-1820)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/31)
  - Photo Unit #: C202 David Doran (l.), Marion Merriman, Major Robert Merriman at Ambite, Nov 1937; 10747 (Item 11-1324)
  - Photo Unit #: C204 Ernest Kozlowski, James Bourne, Ambite, Nov 1937; 10746 (Item 11-0989)
  - Photo Unit #: C215 Wally Sabatini (standing), Political Commissar, Company 3, MacKenzie-Papineau and Egan Schmidt, Oct 1937; 10745 (Item 11-0771)
  - Photo Unit #: C223 British Battalion, (1) J.L. Walker (2), A. MacIntosh (3), F. West (4) F. O'Brien--"Hammersmith Boys", Dec 1937; 10744 (Item 11-1325)
  - Photo Unit #: C228 [?] Reis, Com. David (Red) Drummond, Political Commissar, Machine-Gunner Company, Lincoln-Washington, Oct 1937; 10743 (Item 11-0772)
  - Photo Unit #: C229 [?] (l.), John Robinson and Langston Hughes, Fuentes, Oct 1937; 10742 (Item 11-0773)
  - Photo Unit #: C234 Brigade Machine-Gunner Company, Ambite, Dec 1937; 10741 (Item 11-0990)
  - Photo Unit #: C236 Transmiciones [Transmissions] of 15th Brigade, Dec 1937; 10740 (Item 11-0991)
  - Photo Unit #: C237 Trans. [?] [Isador] Frank Barcena and Patrick Read, Ambite, Dec 1937; 10739 (Item 11-0992)
  - Photo Unit #: C238 Intendencia, Mondejar, Dec 1937; 10738 (Item 11-0993)
  - Photo Unit #: C242 Rifle team of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Dec 1937; 10737 (Item 11-0994)
  - Photo Unit #: C247 Otto Reeves (l.) and Frank Alexander of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Dec 1937; 10736 (Item 11-0995)
  - Photo Unit #: C251 Captain Nilo Makela, MacKenzie-Papineau, and Captain Edward Cecil Smith, Dec 1937; 10735 (Item 11-1326)
  - Photo Unit #: C252 Group of MacKenzie-Papineau [with banner], Dec 1937; 10734 (Item 11-1327)
  - Photo Unit #: C253 Captain Alfredo Balsa, José María Varela, Political Commissar of 24th Battalion, Dec 1937; 10733 (Item 11-0996)
  - Photo Unit #: C255 David Doran, José María Varela at Larance, Captain Alfredo Balsa, John Gates, Political Commissar, Dec 1937; 10732 (Item 11-0997)
  - Photo Unit #: C257 American and Spaniards in 24th [Brigade?] Machine-Gunner Company, Dec 1937; 10731 (Item 11-0998)
  - Photo Unit #: C263 15th Brigade Hospital Corps at Alcorisa, Dec 1937; 10730 (Item 11-0999)
  - Photo Unit #: C264 Ambulance drivers of the 15th Brigade [in front of ambulance] [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Dec 1937; 369370 (Item 11-1888)
  - Photo Unit #: C265 Nurses of 15th Brigade, Dec 1937; 10729 (Item 11-1000)
  - Photo Unit #: C266 Ambulance drivers [of the 15th Brigade in front of Illinois State International Labor Defense ambulance] [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Dec 1937; 369371 (Item 11-1889)
  - Photo Unit #: C267 Doctors of the 15th Brigade [in front of Artists Union ambulance] [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Dec 1937; 369372 (Item 11-1890)
  - Photo Unit #: C268 Doctor Edward Barsky and Doctor [?], Dec 1937; 10728 (Item 11-1001)